Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - United Fruit Company. Van Diepen, William T., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture. Knoblauch, H.C., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Service. Hall, David G.; Pesticides., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture Farm Policy in the Year Ahead, National Advisory Council Report. Freeman, Orville L., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Director of Science and Education. Brady, Nyle C., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture. Freeman, Orville L., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - United States Dept, of Health, Education and Welfare., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture Soil Conservation Service, 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 65-66)
  - V Miscellaneous. Visek, Willard J., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Velsicol Corporation. Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - W Miscellaneous. Watts, Robert E.; Winter, William E., 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - President Perkins. Perkins, James A.; Long, Franklin A., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - President's Report. Perkins, James A., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Provost Dale R. Corson. Corson, Dale R.; Ward, William B.; Cornell University, Office of the Provost; SUNY., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs. Sproull, Robert L.; Allee, David J., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs. Summerskill, John; Crowder, Loy V., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Vice President for Research and Advanced Study. Long, Franklin A.; Stutz, Frederick H., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - C.E. Palm, Talks., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Dean's Luncheon. Ballagh, Tom., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Deans and Directors Meetings., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Deans Meeting, New York City Program. Corson, Dale R.; Sproull, Robert L., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Associate Dean. Kennedy, W. Keith; Pimentel, David., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Director of Admissions. Tetlow, William L.; Storandt, Robert W.; Cornell University, Office of Admissions; Women students; Quotas., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Quota., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Advisers Meeting., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Luykx, Nicolaas G.M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Story, Robert P.; Spencer, Leland; Jewel Tea Company., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Earle, Wendell G.; Luykx, Nicolaas G.M.; How, R. Brian; Jewel Tea Company., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Food Production and Processing, Agricultural Economics. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Agricultural Engineering. French, Orval C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Engineering., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Agricultural Leaders Forum. Kennedy, Robert F.; Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Steciak, Stephen (Mrs.); Park, Roy H.; National Fanners Organization., 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Agricultural Research Conference 23-25 FEB 1966. Freeman, Orville L. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Agricultural and Technical Committee. Hertel, John P., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Agronomy. Cline, Marlin G.; Arnold, Richard W.; Stone, Earl L.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agronomy., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Roadside Spraying for Weed Control, Agronomy.. Cline, Marlin G.; Right-of-way Resources of America., 1963-66 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association. King, Joseph P.; McCalmon, Byron G., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Animal Husbandry. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Animal Husbandry; Holstein-Friesian Association of America., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Apple Committee Meeting on Mechanical Harvesting. Mechanical harvesting., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Associate Coordinator of Research. Rogers, Thomas R., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Bailey Hortorium. Lawrence, George H.M.; Moore, Harold E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Bailey Hortorium., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence on Division of Biology. Morison, Robert S.; Cornell University, Division of Biological Sciences., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University, Division of Biological Sciences, Committee Report to Provost Corson. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Council. Stewart, James P., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University, Cornell United Religious Work., 1966 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council. King, Joseph P., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Counsel. Stamp, Neal R., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Dairy and Food Science. Dondero, Norman C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Dairy and Food Science., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Dairy Situation Report. Milk industry., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Dean's List., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Eastman Stage. Foster, Edward S., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - School of Education. Stutz, Frederick H., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Elevator Installation, Roberts Hall. SUNY Construction Fund., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - College of Agriculture, Undergraduate Enrollment Figures. Harden, Leigh H., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Engineering. Cornell University College of Engineering., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Entomology. Gyrisco, George G.; Pimentel, David; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology; Dutch Elm Disease., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Experiment Station, Geneva. Chapman, P.J.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Barton, Donald W.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Experiment Station, Ithaca. Metz, Joseph F.; Holley, Robert W.; Wilson, John T.; Robison, Howard W.; National Science Foundation., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Lucey Farm, Geneva, New York. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Experiment Station Study Committee Report. Barton, Donald W., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Wellington Property, Geneva, New York., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Seed Processing and Storage Building, Proposed. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Family Camping Area Management Conference., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Hatch Allocation, Experiment Station. Metz, Joseph F., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Experiment Station, Ithaca. Brady, Nyle C.; Christner, Paul; Kennedy, W. Keith; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; National Science Foundation., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - New York State Cooperative Extension Service. Johnson, Alvin A.; Blakeley, Ransom; Swan, John C.; Pease, Wilbur F., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 49-51)
  - Extension Service, Food For Freedom Task Force Report. New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Food For Freedom., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Extension Teaching and Information. Ward, William B.; Kim, Yong H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Extension Teaching and Information., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Extension, Associate Director. Harrington, Clifford R., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Cornell's Role in Extension and Public Functions. Johnson, Alvin A.; Risley, Robert F.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Becky Hammond Situation. Creal, Harold L.; Hammond, Becky., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - County Extension Service Association Law. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - State Leaders Office. Pease, Wilbur F.; Fish, Lois W., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Rockland County Extension Conference on Natural Beauty. Caplan, Ira; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Rockland Foundation., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Campbell, Howard H., 1963-66 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Extension Teaching and Information, New Bulletin Storage., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Proposals for Changes in Name, Administrative Organization Letterhead and Penalty Titles for New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Personnel Actions for Extension. Sproull, Robert L., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Extension Five-County Community and Resource Development Project., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Extension Leaders and Cooperative Extension Agents., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Extension Leaders and 4-H Personnel. Pease, Wilbur F.; Four-H Club., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Extension Veterinarian. Haynes, N. Bruce., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Interdepartmental Research and Extension Program. Brady, Nyle C., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Pesticides Program. Dewey, James E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Pesticides., 1964-66 (Box 22, Folder 69-72)
  - 4-H Office. Stout, Phyllis E.; Pease, Wilbur F.; Four-H Club., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Finance and Business Office. Walsh, Robert L.; Cornell University, Finance and Business Office., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Membership in Faculty of Agriculture., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - University Faculty, Kahn-Bower Report on Kahn, Alfred E.; Quality of Undergraduate Instruction. Murphy, Royse P.; Cornell University, University Faculty., 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - University Faculty. Murphy, Royse P.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Cornell University, University Faculty., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Faculty, College of Agriculture. Watkins, Thomas C., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Applicants., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Departmental Faculty Listings for Planned Program Development. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Farm Research Review Committee. Konkle, Ward W., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture. Seeley, John G.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Food Processing Extension Advisory, 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - UOlHHIlLLcc. Farkas, Daniel F.; Food processing. (Box 23)
  - Food Science Reports. Adams, Morton; Food processing., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Language Requirement for Graduate School, Hartman Report. Hartman, John D., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Student Office. Kizilbash, Mehdi; Cornell University, Foreign Student Office., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Visitors Contact Office. Autret, M., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School. Cooke, W. Donald; Demorest, Jean-Jacques; Cornell University Graduate School; United States Selective Service System., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Student Quotas. Cornell University Graduate School; Quotas., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Student Recruitment., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Graduates, September., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Honors Convocation. Murphy, Royse P., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ho-Nun-De-Kah Faculty-Senior-Parent Reception. New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Ho-Nun-De-Kah Barbegue. Hertel, John P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Laboratory for Cell Physiology, Growth and Development. Chapouthier, F.F.; Steward, F.C.; Corson, Dale R.; National Institute of Health., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Latin American Year. Ellenbogen, Bert L.; Davis, Tom E.; Cornell University, Cornell Latin America Year., 1964-66 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Library. Powell, Whiton., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Los Banos. Kennedy, W. Keith; Case, Harry L.; Turk, Kenneth L.; Trimberger, George W.; Umali, D.L.; Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1964-65 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Planned Maintenance, College of Agriculture., 1964-66 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Marketing and Food Science. Call, David L.; Food processing., 1962-66 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Myers, William I., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University News Bureau., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - School of Nutrition. Barnes, Richard H.; Cornell University, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Parents Weekend. Rubenstein, Allan., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Office. Willers, Diedrich K.; Cornell University, Personnel Office., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Discussions with Department Heads About Key Personnel., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Cornell University Aerial Photographic Resources Institute., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Promotions Recommendations. Watkins, Thomas C., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Plantations. Rockwell, George H.; Wright, T.P.; Cornell Plantations., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Plant Breeding. Plaisted, Robert L.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Plant Breeding, Biometrics. Urquhart, N. Scott; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding, Biometrics Unit., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Plant Pathology. Korf, Richard P.; Kent, George C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Statement of Policy Regarding Participation in Political Activities by Cornell Participants. Political activities., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Policy Statements from Various University Sources., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Pomology. Hoffman, Melvin B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Pomology., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Poultry Husbandry. Young, Robert J.; Bruckner, Jacob H.; Rock, James S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Science., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Publications., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Registrar. Williams, Herbert H.; Cornell University, Office of the Registrar., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Resident Instruction. Hertel, John P.; Watkins, Thomas C.; Buszek, Beatrice R.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction, 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Resident Instruction, Admission Procedures. Cornell, Ezra; Ladd, Robert D.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Resident Instruction, Policy on Handling Students in Trouble. Teitelbaum, Harry; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Resident Instruction, Profile of Students. New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Material to Study Commission from Resident Instruction. Tyler, Howard S.; Hertel, John P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 48-49)
  - Regional Resources and Development Office., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Rural Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; Fischer, Richard B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education; United States Office of Education; Inter-University Program., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Rural Sociology. Larson, Olaf F.; Taietz, Philip; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Sociology., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Rural Youth of Low Income Families, Extension Report. Pease, Wilbur F.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Rustyak Situation. Rustyak, Joseph C., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Science Leaflet. Rockcastle, Verne N., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Status, Prospects, and Needs of the College of Arts and Sciences Report to the President by Dean Brown. Brown, Stuart M.; Cornell University, College of Arts and Sciences, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Study Committee. Adams, Morton., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 57-59)
  - Netherlands Exchange Student. Eijsvoogel, Ir. W. F., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - P ? gi J-BUir, Marsha. Hurd, T. Norman., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Sugar Beet Advisory Committee. Stanton, Bernard F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Sugar Beet Advisory Committee., 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Meeting between Presidents Perkins and Gould. Perkins, James A., 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Treasurer's Office. Cornell University, Office of the Treasurer; Anna Allen Wright Endowment Funds., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Treasurer., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - TV Educational Function of the Colleges of Agriculture and Home Economics., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Committee of undergraduate Programs Abroad. Lathwell, Douglas J., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - The Universities and the Arts. Perkins, James A., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - University Rotations. Mareham, John., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Vegetable Crops. Munger, Henry M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Vegetable Crops., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - New York State Veterinary College. Poppensiek, George C., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Water Supply Seminar, Rural. i Foss, E.W., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - A Miscellaneous. American Institute of Biological Sciences., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Adams, Morton., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - United States Agency for International Development. Maltby, Lucy M.; Turk, Kenneth L., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Aglibut, Andres P., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Agricultural Businessmen's Council. Billings, Russell R.; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Agricultural Adjustments. Hedlund, Glenn W., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Agricultural Hall of Fame and National Agricultural Center., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Agricultural Research Institute., 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Agriculture's Needs, Presented to Senator Kennedy's Staff., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Science Youth Program. Cushman, Harold R.; Bail, Joe P., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Agway, Inc. Dirksen, Everett M.; Milliman, Thomas E.; King, Joseph P.; Fallon, Edmund H.; Ranney, Warren A., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - American Agriculturist Foundation. Hall, A. James., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - B Miscellaneous. Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Brinkley, Parke C.; Blixt, Ira., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Beacon Feeds Division of Textron., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - C Miscellaneous. Cole, Ernest J.; Conklin, Gordon; Campbell Soup Company., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Tree Growers Conference. Bond, Maurice C.; Christmas tree industry., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - D Miscellaneous. DeGraff, Herrell; Dake, Merrills L., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Dairy Herd Improvement Association., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - E Miscellaneous. Eisenhower College., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Empire State Soil Fertility Association. Ervin, John K., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Empire State Potato Club. Amidon, Richard B., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Entomological Society of America. Pimentel, David., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - F Miscellaneous. Fosbrink, Raleigh H.; Freeman, Orville L., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - SUNY Agricultural and Technical Institute at Farmingdale., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Farm Credit Banks of Springfield. Cameron, Gordon., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - New York Farm Electrification Council. Price, Donald R., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - United States Food and Drug Administration. Retzlaff, Allen T.; Larrick, George P., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation. Hill, F.F., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation Report on "Plan Chapmgo.", 1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation Latin America Program, Agricultural Sciences., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Foundation for American Agriculture. Davis, John H.; Bennett, Charles Dana; National Farm-City Committee, Inc., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 23-25)
  - Freeville Property. Kennedy, W. Keith; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Vegetable. Crops., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - G Miscellaneous. Gant, Edward V.; Gyrisco, George G., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Gamma Alpha., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Genesee Valley Regional Market Authority. King, Joseph P.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Governor's Council on Natural Beauty., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Governor's Office. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Maldonado, Alvaro; Whitman, Ann C., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Governor's Program, Agricultural Industry in New York State. Marshall, Alton G.; Dairy farming; Dairy industry., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Governor's Program, Harmful Effects on Animals. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Radiation-, 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Greenhouses and Growth Chambers. Fitzgerald, John; Adinolfi, Anthony G.; Kent, George C.; Greenhouses; Growth chambers., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - H Miscellaneous. Hopper, Nelson F.; Hamilton, Thomas H., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - High School Projects in the Biological Sciences. Roelofs, Faith., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Insurance., 1962-66 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - International Agricultural Development. Turk, Kenneth L.; New York State College of Agriculture, International Agricultural Development; United States Agency for International Development., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 38-39)
  - J Miscellaneous. Johnson, Elton L.; Javits, Jacob K., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - K Miscellaneous. Kane, Robert J., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - L Miscellaneous. Lerch, Donald., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Land Grant College Fund Cuts. Perkins, James A.; Adams, Morton., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 44-46)
  - La Plante, Al A. Hardy, D. Elmo., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Liberian Contract. Gibson, Anson W.; Ma, Paul C.; Wright, Carlton E.; Colman, Gould P.; Univ. of Liberia; Rockefeller Foundation., 1961-66 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - M Miscellaneous. Meyer, William F.; Malott, Deane W., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Maps, County. Wright, Albert H., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - McDonald Farms. McJunkin, Reed L.; J.M. McDonald Foundation-, 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - McDonald Farms Advisory Committee. Sly, K.C.; J.M. McDonald Foundation., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Medical Schools., 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Unprocessed records (Box 25-82)
  - Pesticide Residue (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Extension-statement of scope (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Research programs in the Ag School and Experiment Stations, 1950's (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1957-1958 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Traveling Fellowships, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Vocational Agriculture Conference, 6/18/59 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Program, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Standardization of Milk (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Radio Talks, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Northeastern Project on Pesticide Residues, 1957-59 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Future Trends in Plant Breeding Research - Meeting of USDA Research Administrators; Summary Info from 1957 annual report to Cooperative Grange League Fed. Exchange, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 11)